Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1970s - 1990s, bulk 1980s; 1980-1989; B
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Administration - Miriam Thompson; Jane R. Stern (83-0914-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1806)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Applications - Miriam Thompson; Jane R. Stern (83-0914-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1807)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Finance - Miriam Thompson; Jane R. Stern (83-0914-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1808)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Reports, Publications - Miriam Thompson; Jane R. Stern (83-0914-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1809)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Administration - Miriam Thompson; Marilyn Gittell (81-0800-81), 1981 (Box 161, Folder 1810)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Application - Miriam Thompson; Marilyn Gittell (81-0800-81), 1981 (Box 161, Folder 1811)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Finance - Miriam Thompson; Marilyn Gittell (81-0800-81), 1981 (Box 161, Folder 1812)
    - Advocates for the Children of New York - Report - Miriam Thompson; Marilyn Gittell (81-0800-81), 1981 (Box 161, Folder 1813)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Final Report - Stephen A. Richardson (82-0460-73), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1814)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Publications - Stephen A. Richardson (82-0460-73), 1976-1985 (Box 161, Folder 1815)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Reports - Stephen A. Richardson (82-0460-73), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1816)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Administration - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1817)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Application - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1982 (Box 161, Folder 1818)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Bibliography - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), after 1985 (Box 161, Folder 1819)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Final Report - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 1820)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Finance - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1984-1986 (Box 161, Folder 1821)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - General Correspondence - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1822)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (83-0881-00), 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1823)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Application - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1980 (Box 162, Folder 1824)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Administration - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1980-1985 (Box 162, Folder 1825)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Final Report - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 1826)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Finance - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1982-1985 (Box 162, Folder 1827)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Publications - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1990 (Box 162, Folder 1828)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Reports, Progress - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1982 (Box 162, Folder 1829)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0741-80), 1980 (Box 162, Folder 1830)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Administration - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1980-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1831)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Application - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1980 (Box 162, Folder 1832)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Final Report - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 1833)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Finance - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1980-1983 (Box 162, Folder 1834)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - General Correspondence - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1987 (Box 162, Folder 1835)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Publications - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1990 (Box 162, Folder 1836)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D.; Dorothy J. Jessop, Ph.D. (80-0742-80), 1980 (Box 162, Folder 1837)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Final Report - Ruth E. K. Stein, M.D. (83-0881-00), 1987 (Box 162, Folder 1838)
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association - Administration - Frederic D. Burg, M.D. (83-0911-00), 1983-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1839)
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association - Application - Frederic D. Burg, M.D. (83-0911-00), 1983 (Box 163, Folder 1840)
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association - Bibliography - Frederic D. Burg, M.D. (83-0911-00), after 1987 (Box 163, Folder 1841)
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association - Finance - Frederic D. Burg, M.D. (83-0911-00), 1983-1989 (Box 163, Folder 1842)
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association - Publications, Reports - Frederic D. Burg, M.D. (83-0911-00), 1984-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1843)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Administration - Ned W. Smull, M.D.; Gerald Hughes, M.D. (81-0765-81), 1981-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1844)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Application - Ned W. Smull, M.D.; Gerald Hughes, M.D. (81-0765-81), 1980-1981 (Box 163, Folder 1845)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Final Report - Ned W. Smull, M.D.; Gerald Hughes, M.D. (81-0765-81), 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1846)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Finance - Ned W. Smull, M.D.; Gerald Hughes, M.D. (81-0765-81), 1982-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1847)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Publication - Ned W. Smull, M.D.; Gerald Hughes, M.D. (81-0765-81), 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 1848)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Administration - Jean D. Lockhart, M.S. (83-0927-00), 1983 (Box 163, Folder 1849)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Application - Jean D. Lockhart, M.S. (83-0927-00), 1983 (Box 163, Folder 1850)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics - Final Report - Jean D. Lockhart, M.S. (83-0927-00), 1984 (Box 163, Folder 1851)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science - Administration - Martha R. Redden, Ed.D. (77-0602-76), 1976-1977 (Box 163, Folder 1852)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science - Application - Martha R. Redden, Ed.D. (77-0602-76), 1977 (Box 163, Folder 1853)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science - Final Report - Martha R. Redden, Ed.D. (77-0602-76), 1978-1981 (Box 163, Folder 1854)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science - Finance - Martha R. Redden, Ed.D. (77-0602-76), 1978-1981 (Box 163, Folder 1855)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science - Martha R. Redden, Ed.D. (77-0602-76), 1977 (Box 163, Folder 1856)
    - American Association for Gifted Children - Administration - Anne E. Impellizzeri (84-0981-84), 1984-1986 (Box 163, Folder 1857)
    - American Association for Gifted Children - Final Report - Anne E. Impellizzeri (84-0981-84), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 1858)
    - American Association for Gifted Children - Finance - Anne E. Impellizzeri (84-0981-84), 1984-1986 (Box 163, Folder 1859)
    - American Friends Service Committee - Administration - Daniel A. Seeger; Lee Rosenfeld (88-1103-86), 1986-1988 (Box 163, Folder 1860)
    - American Friends Service Committee - Application - Daniel A. Seeger; Lee Rosenfeld (88-1103-86), 1985-1990 (Box 163, Folder 1861)
    - American Friends Service Committee - Final Report - Daniel A. Seeger; Lee Rosenfeld (88-1103-86), 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 1862)
    - American Friends Service Committee - Finance - Daniel A. Seeger; Lee Rosenfeld (88-1103-86), 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 1863)
    - American National Red Cross - Administration - Eleanor Seidman (84-0991-84), 1984-1989 (Box 163, Folder 1864)
    - American National Red Cross - Application - Eleanor Seidman (84-0991-84), 1984-1985 (Box 163, Folder 1865)
    - American National Red Cross - Final Report - Eleanor Seidman (84-0991-84), 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1866)
    - American National Red Cross - Finance - Eleanor Seidman (84-0991-84), 1985-1987 (Box 163, Folder 1867)
    - American Psychiatric Association - Administration - Miles F. Shore, M.D. (82-0802-00), 1982-1985 (Box 164, Folder 1868)
    - American Psychiatric Association - Application - Miles F. Shore, M.D. (82-0802-00), 1980-1984 (Box 164, Folder 1869)
    - American Psychiatric Association - Finance - Miles F. Shore, M.D. (82-0802-00), 1982-1985 (Box 164, Folder 1870)
    - American Reading Council - Administration - Julia R. Palmer (85-1002-85), 1985-1986 (Box 164, Folder 1871)
    - American Reading Council - Application - Julia R. Palmer (85-1002-85), 1984-1986 (Box 164, Folder 1872)
    - American Reading Council - Finance - Julia R. Palmer (85-1002-85), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 1873)
    - American Reading Council - Report - Julia R. Palmer (85-1002-85), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 1874)
    - Argentina - North American Association for the Advancement of Science, Technology and Culture - Administration - Samuel J. Bosch, M.D. (87-1166-87), 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 1875)
    - Argentina - North American Association for the Advancement of Science, Technology and Culture - Application - Samuel J. Bosch, M.D. (87-1166-87), 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 1876)
    - Argentina - North American Association for the Advancement of Science, Technology and Culture - Final Report - Samuel J. Bosch, M.D. (87-1166-87), 1988 (Box 164, Folder 1877)
      Photographs have been moved to Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3571a.
    - Aspira of New York - Administration - Angelo Gonzalez (81-0801-81), 1981-1982 (Box 164, Folder 1878)
    - Aspira of New York - Application - Angelo Gonzalez (81-0801-81), 1981 (Box 164, Folder 1879)
    - Aspira of New York - Final Report - Angelo Gonzalez (81-0801-81), 1983 (Box 164, Folder 1880)
    - Aspira of New York - Administration - Angelo Gonzalez (81-0801-81), 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 1881)
    - Association for the Care of Children's Health - Applicaiton - Beverley H. Johnson (87-1157-87), 1987-1990 (Box 164, Folder 1882)
    - Association for the Care of Children's Health - Final Report - Beverley H. Johnson (87-1157-87), 1988-1989 (Box 164, Folder 1883)
    - Association for the Care of Children's Health - Finance - Beverley H. Johnson (87-1157-87), 1988 (Box 164, Folder 1884)
    - Association for the Care of Children's Health - Reports, Publications - Beverley H. Johnson (87-1157-87), 1988-1993 (Box 164, Folder 1885)
    - Associates for Youth Development - Administration - William A. Lofquist (82-0861-00), 1982-1983 (Box 164, Folder 1886)
    - Associates for Youth Development - Application - William A. Lofquist (82-0861-00), 1982 (Box 164, Folder 1887)
    - Associates for Youth Development - Finance - William A. Lofquist (82-0861-00), 1983 (Box 164, Folder 1888)
    - Associates for Youth Development - Reports - William A. Lofquist (82-0861-00), 1984 (Box 164, Folder 1890-1891)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Administration - Jane Knitzer (84-0996-84), 1988 (Box 165, Folder 1892)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Application - Jane Knitzer (84-0996-84), 1984 (Box 165, Folder 1893)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Final Report - Jane Knitzer (84-0996-84), 1988 (Box 165, Folder 1894-1895)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Finance - Jane Knitzer (84-0996-84), 1988 (Box 165, Folder 1896)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Reports - Jane Knitzer (84-0996-84), 1988 (Box 165, Folder 1897)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Application - Edna Shapiro, Ph.D.; Doris Wallace, Ph.D. (82-0831-00), 1982 (Box 165, Folder 1898)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Finance - Edna Shapiro, Ph.D.; Doris Wallace, Ph.D. (82-0831-00), 1981-1983 (Box 165, Folder 1899)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Report - Edna Shapiro, Ph.D.; Doris Wallace, Ph.D. (82-0831-00), 1984 (Box 165, Folder 1900)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Report - Edna Shapiro, Ph.D.; Doris Wallace, Ph.D. (82-0831-00), 1982 (Box 165, Folder 1901)
    - The Big Sisters - Administration - John A. Jager (82-0851-00), 1982 (Box 165, Folder 1902)
    - The Big Sisters - Application - John A. Jager (82-0851-00), 1982 (Box 165, Folder 1903)
    - The Big Sisters - Finance - John A. Jager (82-0851-00), 1982-1984 (Box 165, Folder 1904)
    - The Big Sisters - Reports - John A. Jager (82-0851-00), 1982-1984 (Box 165, Folder 1905)
    - The Big Sisters - Administration - Larrie Zampini (87-1139-87), 1987-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1906)
    - The Big Sisters - Application - Larrie Zampini (87-1139-87), 1987 (Box 165, Folder 1907)
    - The Big Sisters - Final Report - Larrie Zampini (87-1139-87), 1988-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1908)
    - The Big Sisters - Finance - Larrie Zampini (87-1139-87), 1987-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1909)
    - Black Spectrum Theater Company - Administration - Carl Clay (83-0907-00), 1983-1984 (Box 166, Folder 1910)
    - Black Spectrum Theater Company - Application - Carl Clay (83-0907-00), 1983 (Box 166, Folder 1911)
    - Black Spectrum Theater Company - Finance - Carl Clay (83-0907-00), 1984-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1912)
    - Black Spectrum Theater Company - General Correspondence - Carl Clay (83-0907-00), 1984-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1913)
    - Black Spectrum Theater Company - Carl Clay (83-0907-00), 1984 (Box 166, Folder 1914)
    - Boston University - Administration - Joel J. Alpert, M.D. (84-0984-84), 1984-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1915)
    - Boston University - Application - Joel J. Alpert, M.D. (84-0984-84), 1984 (Box 166, Folder 1916)
    - Boston University - Final Report - Joel J. Alpert, M.D. (84-0984-84), 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1917)
    - Boston University - Finance - Joel J. Alpert, M.D. (84-0984-84), 1984-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1918)
    - Boys Club of America - Administration - David F. Wynn (82-0842-00), 1980-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1919)
    - Boys Club of America - Application - David F. Wynn (82-0842-00), 1982 (Box 166, Folder 1920)
    - Boys Club of America - Finance - David F. Wynn (82-0842-00), 1982-1983 (Box 166, Folder 1921)
    - Boys Club of America - General Correspondence - David F. Wynn (82-0842-00), 1982 (Box 166, Folder 1922)
    - Boys Club of America - Reports - David F. Wynn (82-0842-00), 1981-1983 (Box 166, Folder 1923)
    - Boys Club of New York - Administration - Robert Olson (83-0807-82), 1982-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1924)
    - Boys Club of New York - Finance - Robert Olson (83-0807-82), 1982 (Box 166, Folder 1925)
    - Boys Club of New York - Application - Robert Olson (84-0807-82) (82-0807-00) (84-0401-88), 1981-1984 (Box 166, Folder 1926)
    - Boys Club of New York - Administration - Robert Olson (86-1102-86), 1986-1987 (Box 166, Folder 1927)
    - Boys Club of New York - Application - Robert Olson (86-1102-86), 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1928)
    - Boys Club of New York - Finance - Robert Olson (86-1102-86), 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1986)
    - Boys Club of New York - General Correspondence - Robert Olson (86-1102-86), 1987 (Box 166, Folder 1930)
    - Boys Club of New York - Reports - Robert Olson (86-1102-86), 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1931a)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Administration - Richard L. Williams (87-1176-87), 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1931b)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Application - Richard L. Williams (87-1176-87), 1987-1990 (Box 167, Folder 1932)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Finance - Richard L. Williams (87-1176-87), 1987-1989 (Box 167, Folder 1933)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Report - Richard L. Williams (87-1176-87), 1989 (Box 167, Folder 1934)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Centers - James Canellas - Administration (85-1039-85), 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 1935)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Centers - James Canellas - Applications (85-1039-85), 1983-1988 (Box 167, Folder 1936)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Centers - James Canellas - Finance (85-1039-85), 1985-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1937)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Centers - James Canellas - Reports (85-1039-85), 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1938)
    - The Brookings Institution - Administration - Bruce K. MacLaury (85-1044-85), 1985-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1939)
    - The Brookings Institution - Application - Bruce K. MacLaury (85-1044-85), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 1940)
    - The Brookings Institution - Correspondence - Bruce K. MacLaury (85-1044-85), 1985-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1941)
    - The Brookings Institution - Final Report - Bruce K. MacLaury (85-1044-85), 1988 (Box 167, Folder 1942)
    - The Brookings Institution - Finance - Bruce K. MacLaury (85-1044-85), 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1943)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service - Administration - Donna A. Santarsiero (85-1040-85), 1985-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1944)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service - Application - Donna A. Santarsiero (85-1040-85), 1985-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1945)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Administration - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), 1986-1988 (Box 167, Folder 1946)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Application - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1947)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Bibliography - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), after 1988 (Box 167, Folder 1948)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Finance - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), 1986-1988 (Box 167, Folder 1949)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Publications - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), 1988 (Box 167, Folder 1950)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Jack Block, Ph.D. (86-1121-86), 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1951)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Patricia Greenfield (87-1191-87), 1993 (Box 167, Folder 1951b)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Administration - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), 1984-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1952)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Application - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), 1984-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1953)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Bibliography - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), after 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1954)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Final Report - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1955)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Finance - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), 1984-1986 (Box 168, Folder 1956)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Publications, Reports/Manuscripts - Leonard I. Pearlin, Ph.D. (83-0939-00), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1957)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Administration - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1987-1989 (Box 168, Folder 1958)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Application - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1986-1990 (Box 168, Folder 1959)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Final Report - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1990 (Box 168, Folder 1960)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Finance - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1987-1990 (Box 168, Folder 1961)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Reports, Publications - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1990 (Box 168, Folder 1962)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Lenore C. Terr, M.D. (86-1071-01), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1963)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Administration - Joanna H. Fannos (83-0934-00), 1985-1986 (Box 168, Folder 1964)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Application - Joanna H. Fannos (83-0934-00), 1983-1984 (Box 168, Folder 1965)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Finance - Joanna H. Fannos (83-0934-00), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1966)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Reports - Joanna H. Fannos (83-0934-00), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1967)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Final Report - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1968)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Reports - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), 1984 (Box 168, Folder 1969)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Application - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), 1981-1984 (Box 168, Folder 1970)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Bibliography - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), after 1984 (Box 168, Folder 1971)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Administration - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), 1982-1986 (Box 168, Folder 1972)
    - California School of Professional Psychology, Berkeley - Finance - John A. Martin, Ph.D. (82-0852-00), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1973)
    - Cambridge University Press - Administration - Susan Milmoe (84-0942-84), 1984 (Box 168, Folder 1974)
    - Cambridge University Press - Application - Susan Milmoe (84-0942-84), 1983-1984 (Box 168, Folder 1975)
    - Cambridge University Press - Finance - Susan Milmoe (84-0942-84), 1984 (Box 168, Folder 1976)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - Administration - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1984-1986 (Box 168, Folder 1977)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - Application - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1983-1984 (Box 168, Folder 1978)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - Final Report - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1986-1990 (Box 169, Folder 1979)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - Finance - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1986 (Box 169, Folder 1980)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - General Correspondence - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1985 (Box 169, Folder 1981)
    - Camp Fire, Inc. - Reports - Arnold E. Sherman (86-0945-84), 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1982)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - Administration - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1982-1987 (Box 169, Folder 1983)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - Applications - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1982-1987 (Box 169, Folder 1984)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - Final Report - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1985-1987 (Box 169, Folder 1985)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - Finance - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1985-1987 (Box 169, Folder 1986)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - General Correspondence - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1984 (Box 169, Folder 1987)
    - Canaan Senior Service Center, Inc. - Reports - Doris L. Mason (85-0974-84), 1984-1987 (Box 169, Folder 1988)
    - Casita Maria Settlement House - Administration - Edward Pabon; Christina Toosie (82-0863-00), 1983-1984 (Box 169, Folder 1989)
    - Casita Maria Settlement House - Application - Edward Pabon; Christina Toosie (82-0863-00), 1982-1989 (Box 169, Folder 1990)
    - Casita Maria Settlement House - Finance - Edward Pabon; Christina Toosie (82-0863-00), 1985 (Box 169, Folder 1991)
    - Casita Maria Settlement House - General Correspondence - Edward Pabon; Christina Toosie (82-0863-00), 1984-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1992)
    - Casita Maria Settlement House - Reports - Edward Pabon; Christina Toosie (82-0863-00), 1984-1985 (Box 169, Folder 1993)
    - Catholic Big Brothers of New York - Sister Cecil Kavai - Administration (84-0987-84), 1984 (Box 169, Folder 1994)